[
  {
    "name": "geography",
    "questions_answers": [
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of Japan?",
        "answer": "tokyo"},
      {
        "question": "Which country is the Kremlin located in?",
        "answer": "russia"},
      {
        "question": "How many states does the USA have?",
        "answer": "50"},
      {
        "question": "What is the dominant language of Belgium?",
        "answer": "french"},
      {
        "question": "What is the country to the south of Mt. Everest?",
        "answer": "nepal"},
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
        "answer": "brasilia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which lake does the Nile come from?",
        "answer": "victoria"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country has a flag featuring a purple parrot in it?",
        "answer": "dominica"
      },
      {
        "question": "Spell the capital of Burkina Faso correctly.",
        "answer": "ouagadougou"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country uses long white license plates with blue text, featuring a Mokorotlo in it?",
        "answer": "lesotho"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "history",
    "questions_answers": [
      {
        "question": "What country was ruled by Pharaohs?",
        "answer": "egypt"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the oldest known civilization?",
        "answer": "sumer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which river is the birthplace of Chinese civilization?",
        "answer": "yellow"
      },
      {
        "question": "What were the feudal lords of the Samurai called?",
        "answer": "daimyo"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the lingua franca of the Aztecs?",
        "answer": "nahuatl"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the period of warring states called in Japan?",
        "answer": "sengoku jidai"
      },
      {
        "question": "What were Roman baths called?",
        "answer": "thermae"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Zulu king led the Zulus in the Anglo-Zulu war?",
        "answer": "cetshwayo"
      },
      {
        "question": "What year was Benito Mussolini's March on Rome?",
        "answer": "1922"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Yuan dynasty leader launched a naval expedition to punish Kertanegara?",
        "answer": "kublai khan"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "anime",
    "questions_answers": [
      {
        "question": "What is Goku's signature technique?",
        "answer": "kamehameha"
      },
      {
        "question": "What famous jutsu in Naruto takes the form of a spinning ball of chakra?",
        "answer": "rasengan"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which dere archetype is known for showing love and obsession to the point of being dangerously possessive and violent?",
        "answer": "yandere"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Izuku Midoriya's hero name?",
        "answer": "deku"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of magic is used by Megumin?",
        "answer": "explosion"
      },
      {
        "question": "What stand does Jotaro Kujo use?",
        "answer": "star platinum"
      },
      {
        "question": "What great tomb is the headquarters of Ainz Ooal Gown?",
        "answer": "nazarick"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which anime studio animated the first season of One-Punch Man?",
        "answer": "mad house"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which dere archetype is used to describe someone with a God-complex?",
        "answer": "kamidere"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the one Danganronpa character that loves Bojobo dolls?",
        "answer": "kyoko kirigiri"
      }
    ]
  }
]